axa.co.uk 2014-12-13

# Privacy Policy | AXA UK

  * AXA UK plc (“AXA UK”) is part of the AXA Group of companies, which take your privacy very seriously. This  Privacy Policy  tells you, in broad terms, how we use personal information that we collect from your use of the domain http://www.axa.co.uk (the ” **Website** ”) and all sub-domains of  the Website.

This Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use (together the “ **Terms and Conditions** ”) apply to your use of the Website. Please read the Terms and Conditions carefully.

By proceeding with access to the Website you are deemed to have accepted the Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree with the Terms and Conditions, then please refrain from accessing or using the Website. 

Any personal information you supply to AXA UK via the Website (and by other means) will be treated in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other legislation intended to protect your personal information and privacy (see **Your Personal Data and Your Legal Rights** ).

We may revise the Privacy Policy at any time by amending this page. You are expected to check this page from time to time to take notice of any changes we make, as they are binding on you. 

The Website has links to websites of other companies within the AXA Group and to selected third party websites. Each AXA Group company’s website will contain similar details to those set out below, but which may be more specific to their business and we recommend that you check these if you visit their websites. We also recommend that you check the terms and conditions and privacy statements on all external websites before using such websites (see **Third Party Links** ).

### Cookies

AXA UK sends cookies to your computer from the Website. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disc for record keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Internet more useful to you because they contain information about your preferences on particular websites, which allows website owners to provide more useful features for their users. For more information on Cookies please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>. 

AXA UK uses cookies and tracking software to monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage in order to develop the design and layout of the Website to better meet the needs of visitors to the Website. This will include non-specific data such as mouse-movements and pages visited.

 Should you wish to refuse to accept cookies or  restrict the data that we collect through our tracking software, you can alter your cookies setting in your browser. However, if you choose to alter your cookies setting in your browser you may be unable to access parts of the Website.

More detailed information on the cookies we store and their use can be found on our cookie policy page.

### What Information Do We Collect and How?

The personal information AXA UK collects through the Website may include details such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number and date of birth and bank or credit card details. 

Personal information is collected by AXA UK on the Website:

    * via enquiry, registration, claim forms, feedback forms and forums;
    * when you purchase any of our products or services;
    * when you fill out a survey, or vote in a poll on this website;
    * through applications;
    * through feedback forms and web analytics tags; and
    * when you provide your details to us either online or offline.

We may also use cookies or similar technologies to collect website usage information. For further information, please see the section on Cookies above. In addition we may also collect IP addresses via a web analytics package.

### What Will the Information We Collect Be Used For?

We may use the information we collect to send you information about our products and services and any other services described in our Website. We may also use the information we collect for analytical purposes and to assist us in improving our processes, products and services. We will also use information collected to safe-guard against fraud and money laundering. We are required to report details of some suspicious activities to the Serious Organised Crime Agency (“ **SOCA** ”).

If you provide personal information via the Website, you will be told what the information you provide will be used for before the information is submitted to us and you will have the chance to withhold or withdraw your consent for a use other than as listed above. We may send this information in confidence to companies within the AXA Group and other companies acting on our instructions, including those outside of the European Economic Area.

### Security of Personal Data

AXA UK will take all reasonable steps to ensure that any personal data that you provide via the Website is kept secure. Although we endeavour to protect your personal data, because of the nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Website and any inward transmission of data is carried out at your own risk.

### Your Personal Data and Your Legal Rights

Any personal information you supply to AXA UK via the Website or via any third party website will be treated in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003.

AXA UK is committed to delivering the rights that the Data Protection Act 1998 and Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations provides to individuals. Amongst these are:

    * the right to object to your personal information being used for direct marketing. We will give you the ability to object to this, and where required we will ensure we obtain your consent before undertaking marketing; and
    * the right to request a copy of the personal information AXA UK holds about you.  To do this, please write to us with full details of what you require enclosing a cheque or postal order for £10 payable to AXA UK plc, at the following address:

Data Protection Officer  
AXA UK plc  
5 Old Broad Street  
London  
EC2N 1AD

### Errors and Omissions

If you believe that there may be an error in any of the information that you have submitted via the Website, please email: webmaster@axa.co.uk.We will review your records as soon as possible.

### Third Party Links

The Website may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other websites using the links provided, the operators of these websites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

### Consent

We do not intentionally collect any information via the Website from children under 16 years of age, and unless the information was collected in connection with a policy claim, shall delete the details of such users when a parent or guardian notifies us that any details have been obtained from their child.

### Complaints

If you have a complaint in relation to the Website, please contact us at the following address:

 Customer Care  
AXA UK plc  
5 Old Broad Street  
London  
EC2N 1AD

### AXA Group

Wherever the name “AXA” is used on the Website, this implies one or more of the following companies within the AXA Group of companies, which may offer products or services on the Website. Further details can be found on the respective companies’ websites.

AXA Insurance UK plc, trading as AXA Insurance and AXA Solutions, a public company limited by shares incorporated in England and Wales with company number 078950 and whose registered office is at 5 Old Broad Street, London, EC2N 1AD.

Architas Multi-Manager Limited, a private limited company incorporated in England and Wales with company number 06458717 and whose registered office is at 5 Old Broad Street, London, EC2N 1AD.

AXA Portfolio Services Limited, a private limited company incorporated in England and Wales with company number 1128611 and whose registered office is at 5 Old Broad Street, London, EC2N 1AD. AXA Portfolio Services Limited trades as Architas, AXA Self Investor and Architas.

AXA Wealth Services Limited, a private limited company incorporated in England and Wales with company number 02238458 and whose registered office: 5 Old Broad Street, London, EC2N 1AD.

Winterthur Life UK Limited a private limited company incorporated in England and Wales with company number 3116645 and whose registered office is at 5 Old Broad Street, London, EC2N 1AD.

AXA Wealth Limited, a private limited company incorporated  in England and Wales with company number 01225468 and whose registered office is at 5 Old Broad Street, London, EC2N 1AD. 

AXA PPP Healthcare Limited, a private limited company incorporated in England and Wales with company number 03148119 and whose registered office is at 5 Old Broad Street London EC2N 1AD.

Swiftcover Insurance Services Limited, a private limited company incorporated in England and Wales with company number 05298352 and whose registered office is at 5 Old Broad Street London EC2N 1AD.

Bluefin Group Limited, a private limited company incorporated in England and Wales with company number 05936990 and whose registered office is at 5 Old Broad Street London EC2N 1AD.

AXA Direct Limited, a private limited company incorporated in England and Wales with company number 02204119 and whose registered office is at 5 Old Broad Street London EC2N 1AD.

AXA UK plc  
Registered Company Number: 02937724  
Registered Office: 5 Old Broad Street London EC2N 1AD
